karaokeplay.com 2010-11-21

# KaraokePlay Privacy Policy

This is KaraokePlay ("KaraokePlay," "we" or “us”) online Privacy Policy for all websites owned or controlled by KaraokePlay (except as otherwise provided on such site), including www.KaraokePlay.com, and for the Service and Materials provided by KaraokePlay (except as otherwise indicated in such Service or Materials). This policy applies only to information gathered through the Service, including the use of Materials through the Service, but not to other off-line transactions with KaraokePlay, nor to transactions with any third party not owned or controlled by KaraokePlay. By using the Service, and by checking the box indicating agreement with the Terms of Use during registration, you agree to accept the practices and terms set forth in this Privacy Policy. Capitalized terms not defined in this policy shall have the meaning set forth in the KaraokePlay Terms of Use Agreement. ****

**1.      Children**

KaraokePlay does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. KaraokePlay requests that children under the age of 13 not use the Service nor submit any personal information to the Service. Since information regarding children under the age of 13 is not collected, KaraokePlay does not knowingly use or distribute personal information regarding children under the age of 13. If KaraokePlay obtains actual knowledge that it has collected personal information about a child under the age of 13, that information will be immediately deleted from our database.

**2.      Personally Identifiable Information You Provide**

You may also be asked to provide personally identifiable information in order to use certain Services and to obtain support from KaraokePlay. This information may include your name, address, telephone number, credit card number (for paid Services), e-mail address and instant messenger user/screen name, as well as the e-mail addresses, user/screen name and telephone numbers of those to whom you send content. Other Users may also provide us with your e-mail address, user/screen name, or telephone number in order to send you content. If you do not want to provide KaraokePlay with any personally identifiable information, you should not use the Services that require such information.

**3.      Non-Personally identifiable and Aggregate Information**

The non-personally identifiable information that we may gather includes your gender, age, zip code, country or territory of residence, IP address, the type of browser that you use, the type and nature of the content that you upload to the Service and access from the Service, the comments and communication that you enter into the Service, the links and transactions with us and with third-parties that you enter into via the Service, and other aspects of your use of the Service. KaraokePlay uses this information to improve the Service, conduct research, to analyze your and other User’s interest in the areas of the Service, to tailor advertising and content displayed to you and other Users, to inform our suppliers about the use of the Service, and to inform our advertisers about the number of Users that have viewed their advertising. To do this we may combine information that we have about you with information that we obtain from business partners or other companies. We may also release aggregate demographic information about User trends to partners and other third parties, including third-party advertisers on the Service. An example of this type of information would be patterns of use of the Service based on zip code or age group. We also retain aggregated log files of requested content in order to report overall product usage to content partners and to evaluate User trends.

**4.      Use and Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information**

KaraokePlay does not rent or sell personally identifiable information, such as your name or e-mail address, to advertisers.  KaraokePlay may use your personally identifiable information:

    * To deliver you the Service and send you notices related to the Service, your Account and necessary updates. This includes fulfilling your requests for products and services and delivering content to you that is sent by other Users.  
    * To deliver your content to other Users (we will share your User name with Users to whom you send content). If you do not want to share this information, you should limit the content that you share and the Users that you share it with.  
    * To e-mail you our newsletter, promotions and special offers from us and our partners. You may remove yourself from this list at any time by clicking on the appropriate unsubscribe button in the e-mail that we send to you.  
* To manage your Account and Account access, provide you with Software and Materials, purchase confirmations, support and customer service and to keep track of support and customer service requests.  
    * To provide you with information concerning promotions and sweepstakes that you enter (see below for more details).  
    * To determine the technical capabilities of your device and the appropriate content to deliver to you.

KaraokePlay may disclose personally identifiable information to its partners in order to provide the Service, resolve service problems and correct errors in the Service (including customer inquiries, billing and credit corrections), to communicate with you about the Service, to provide you with advertising and promotional information in connection with the Service, and to enhance your experience on the Service. However, these companies do not have an independent right to share this information. Due to our contractual obligations with these third parties and the need to share personally identifiable information to deliver and support the Service, we cannot provide you with the opportunity to opt-out of sharing personally identifiable information with these third parties.

Your personally identifiable information may be provided to a third party if KaraokePlay files for bankruptcy, or there is a transfer of the assets or ownership of KaraokePlay. KaraokePlay may also disclose personally identifiable information in order to respond to a subpoena, court order or other such request, or to otherwise establish or exercise our rights, or defend against legal claims. KaraokePlay may also provide such personally identifiable information order to investigate, prevent and take action regarding fraud or misuse of the Service, to comply with law or in response to a law enforcement agency's request, to enforce our Privacy Policy and end user agreements, and to protect the rights, property and safety of the Service, Users and others.

In addition to other Users that you designate, KaraokePlay, its partners, and each of their contractors and employees may view the content that you upload to the Service in order to provide the Service and otherwise perform the tasks set forth in this Privacy Policy.

Any information that you may reveal in your User profile, in communication with other Users or in other online discussions or forums is intentionally open to the public and is not in any way private. You should think carefully before publicly disclosing any personally identifiable information. What you have written may be seen and/or collected by third parties and may be used by others in ways we are unable to control or predict.

**5.      Cookies and Pixel Tags**

Cookies are small bits of data that are deposited on a User's hard drive. The Service utilizes Cookies and IP addresses for certain functions. Cookies permit Users to store their password and other User information without having to constantly re-enter this data. Cookies also permit KaraokePlay and our advertisers to tailor the Service and advertising to your needs. Some of the advertising served through the Service may be supplied by one or more third parties who may also use cookies. In addition, we may also record the pages you visit on our Service through the use of pixel tags (also called “clear gifs” or “beacons”).

If you wish to delete, modify or update any information KaraokePlay has received, please go to the KaraokePlay Website and select the “My Studio” link.  **____**

**7.      Other Websites and Services**

KaraokePlay is not responsible for the privacy policies of websites and services to which the Service links, or of which the Service is a part. If you provide any information to such third parties different rules regarding the collection and use of your personal information may apply. We strongly suggest you review such third party's privacy policies before providing any data to them.

**8.      Security**   
KaraokePlay takes appropriate steps to help ensure data privacy and security including through various hardware and software methodologies. However, due to the open nature of communication through the Internet, we cannot guarantee that communications between you and the Service, and the Service and you, will be free from unauthorized access by third parties. Users of the Service do so at their own risk. KaraokePlay cannot guarantee the security of any information that is disclosed online.

**9.      Promotions and Sweepstakes**

If you chose to enter a promotion, sweepstakes, or contest hosted by KaraokePlay or sponsored by KaraokePlay and/or one of our partners, we (and/or our promotional partner) may ask for your name, address, and/or email address. You may be asked to provide additional information or to answer certain questions, some of which may be optional, in order to participate. We and/or our partner may contact you in connection with a particular promotion, such as a sweepstakes or contest, in order to update you of your status, administer the promotion, let you know that a promotion has ended, and for other purposes. Promotions that are hosted on the Service may be sponsored by KaraokePlay, may be co-sponsored by KaraokePlay and another company, or may be sponsored by companies other than KaraokePlay. Some or all of the data collected during a promotion may be shared with the sponsor(s) or companies indicated on the entry form. We may use third-party companies to generate and manage some of our promotional campaigns. We may share with these companies Service usage information about those visitors to our web site who participate in the promotional campaigns. This sharing is for the purpose of targeting future campaigns and upgrading visitor information used in reporting statistics.

**10.   Reasonable Efforts**

We will use reasonable efforts to comply with this Privacy Policy and will take prompt corrective action when we learn of any failure to comply with our Privacy Policy. We sometimes release beta versions of our products and services, which are further refined before the release of the final version. Because these products and services are still in a test phase, we may not always catch an unintended privacy issue, despite our efforts to do so. As such, we welcome User feedback on any privacy concerns you may have. In light of the above and because of the complex and constantly changing nature of our technology and business, and the security risks associated with using the Internet, KaraokePlay does not guarantee error-free performance under this Privacy Policy. To the extent permissible under law, KaraokePlay shall not be liable for any incidental, consequential or punitive damages relating to this Privacy Policy.

**11.   Modifications of the Privacy Policy**

KaraokePlay reserves the rights to modify its Privacy Policy at any time and will notify you by posting an amendment to the Privacy Policy on the Service. Such modifications will become effective on the day they are posted. KaraokePlay encourages you to frequently review the Privacy Policy for any modifications.
